Units:
	Change the way we currently do the selecting rectangle into a custom function that looks at selectables (specificaly owned selectables) so we don't need to go over every, from possibly a lot of, physics objects. (Will see about performance)(make the checking in parallel if so.)
	Pathfinding tweeks:
		Avoiding static objects (the whole avoidance thing doesn't really do the avoiding)
	Agro range (range from which the unit automaticaly starts attacking when idle, should be capped from the bottom by highest attack range)
	Attack range(s) (done from code (if there are multiple attacks for the unit))
	If a unit has multiple attacks player can set its main one(globaly, to selection, individually) and the unit will approach for distance required to perform this attack.
	Have them easily scalable (colliders,sprites) so that it can be done easily when needed
	
	
Selectables:
	Highlight upon hover with team allegiance
	Highlighting should be based on Team allegiance. Default is yellow, Friendily is blue, Own is green and Hostile is red
	If in players selection is any non-owned it should not be selected. Only if its a single one.
	Owner: Fake Player or neutral (special kind of player)
	The graphics on units exist for the Device the game is ran on. All the graphics are handled for the Device. Therefore if a Unit is selected it is shown only to a human player. We don't have more than 1 human player active at the same time and therefore all graphics are relevant only to this person. AI players do their own selecting thing but it is naturaly not shown graphicly.
	
Player(Gameplay):
	Fog of War -> a sort of grid overlay with 0(within sight) 1(visible) 2(known) 3(unknown) (3 is only for campaign)
		Interacts with player vision range that changes the cells into zeroes upon entering and to 1 upon leaving
		There is a black...thing (tilemap?) as a visual representation of the fog of war and its alpha chanell is (33%,1) (66%,2) (100%,3)
		ALTERNATIVELY:
		A sprite with a texture that gets blended with a trasnparent one over time.
		But thats just fog of war
		Meaning there would have to be something entirely different for vision.
	Unit selection grouped by unit type -> TABing through groups of same units (need to fix the comparator)
	Units of the same type can be sorted by health or if possible by energy as set by the player in the Unit selection part of the GUI
	Keybindings

Player UI:
	Resizable HUD
	Options menu
	Each player should have their own visibility layer (looks like there are 20 available so 1 is general, 2 is spectator, 3 is reserved just in case and 4-20 are for players)
	->Since we don't have splitscreen we can technicaly have only the first three layers since each player will see different thing anyway. (We do have to handle it for the AI players though)
	Minimap

Buildings:
	Workers and buildingInterface
	Grid will be nice later. For now just stick with checking the collison area.

General:
	Consciously think of multiplayer -> try and have most things separate from the main players interface.
	Think of AI player -> try to have graphics as separate as possible from gameplay.
	That way graphics actually run only in each players vision and since AIs don't have graphical vision it should really help with performance
	Figure out how to actually do graphics only in vision range.

MainMenu: 
	Polish FFA
	F8->MUTE sound effect (Default on)
	F9->Pause
	F10->Stop (Replace with Wallpaper or whatnot)
	Works like a benchmark (If the game crashes it should ask if one wants to play with safe settings, or maybe before the game launches for the first time and then this thing is off otherwise its on by default)
	It could be interactable (drag units on the screen,Dropping bombs etc.)

Map:
	Map borders: Would be lovely if we were to make a special object in C++ that is done as a rectangle without the filling. 
		Then write script that takes the camera and sets its limits the same way

FileManagement:
	Figuere out how to make maps represented as files in separate non-compiled in folder.
	SaveFiles


Linux is lil janky - METHODADD makro don't work in gcc - needs full method signature - missing "godot::[className]::"
before methodname